<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>aswinmohanme</title>
    <link>https://aswinmohan.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on aswinmohanme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright Aswin Mohan</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 21:28:56 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aswinmohan.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Compiling OpenSSL 1.0 for Older Package Versions</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/compiling-older-openssl-for-older-packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 21:28:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/compiling-older-openssl-for-older-packages/</guid>
      <description>Running older versions of software is always a pain. There will be missing libraries, compilation errors and what not. These issues can be mitigated little by using a package manager that manages the different versions of the software. But most package managers such as asdf download the source (yea OSS) and compile on your machine.
Most of the tools and libraries work really good, but there is one error that keeps coming again and again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing Autocomplete Select in Rails 6</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/implementing-autocomplete-in-rails-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 13:24:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/implementing-autocomplete-in-rails-6/</guid>
      <description>simple-form makes creating forms that handle associations in rails a breeze. It creates a select dropdown that works really well for use cases where the number of records are few. But once the number of options in the select box gets over a certain number you would be doing your users a favor by implementing it an autocomplete box.
I ran into the same situation. I had a Contact table that has_one: Panchayat relation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Hosted NPM Fonts with Webpack</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/npm-fonts-on-webpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 12:45:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/npm-fonts-on-webpack/</guid>
      <description>Whenever I wanted new fonts Google Fonts was the defacto place I&amp;rsquo;d go to. It has a ton of great fonts and it&amp;rsquo;s fairly easy to add to your projects. They are also hosted for free by Google which takes some load of your own webserver. I had a personal collection of favorite fonts that I cycle through on new projects.
Everything was going nice when I found out Inter. It was free, looks really crisp and was not available on Google Fonts :(.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Simplest Productivity System is the Best</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/simple-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/simple-productivity/</guid>
      <description>Most of us are productivity gurus on the Internet nowadays. Anyone who works with a computer now has some general ideas of how to achieve productivity and most have those ideas to a fault. There are a million + one articles floating around claiming to have found the secret for eternal productivity. We watch endless motivational videos and informational videos outlining a 99 step process to plan your whole day, another 98 steps to plan your whole week for optimum productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning Off Syntax Highlighting</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/turning-off-syntax-highlighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 09:32:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/turning-off-syntax-highlighting/</guid>
      <description>Few weeks back I stumbled on this blog post which stated the obvious benefits of disabling syntax highlighting for your code. I would have been surprised if I hadn&amp;rsquo;t read this one before. Both the blog posts advocate disabling colors schemes completely or minimally.
At the outset this seems absurd for anyone who has been coding for any length of time and insane for the cool kids who started learning to code in the age of color monitors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 10:28:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Aswin Mohan, 21 years old final-year Computer Science student at College of Engineering Chengannur. I love to code and have been doing that since 2013, I also love designing because who hates beautiful things.
I put most of my code here on github.com/aswinmohanme, and some designs on behance. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to know more about me, here is my resume, my contact details are inside.
 my best work</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Writing on the Internet</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/on-writing-on-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 10:26:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/on-writing-on-internet/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since I have written some long form content, and it&amp;rsquo;s starting to show. The ability to write shows the ability of the mind to sit down and focus. Lately it has been hard to write something down, focus seems to be all over the place. That is hardly surprising given the amount of time I spent on my smartphone.
As important as the writing itself is the Medium(pun intended) and how much control you have over it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>