<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on aswinmohanme</title>
    <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on aswinmohanme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright Aswin Mohan</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 12:45:50 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aswinmohan.me/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Hosted NPM Fonts with Webpack</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/npm-fonts-on-webpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 12:45:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/npm-fonts-on-webpack/</guid>
      <description>Whenever I wanted new fonts Google Fonts was the defacto place I&#39;d go to. It has a ton of great fonts and it&#39;s fairly easy to add to your projects. They are also hosted for free by Google which takes some load of your own webserver. I had a personal collection of favorite fonts that I cycle through on new projects.
Everything was going nice when I found out Inter. It was free, looks really crisp and was not available on Google Fonts :(.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Simplest Productivity System is the Best</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/simple-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/simple-productivity/</guid>
      <description>Most of us are productivity gurus on the Internet nowadays. Anyone who works with a computer now has some general ideas of how to achieve productivity and most have those ideas to a fault. There are a million + one articles floating around claiming to have found the secret for eternal productivity. We watch endless motivational videos and informational videos outlining a 99 step process to plan your whole day, another 98 steps to plan your whole week for optimum productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning Off Syntax Highlighting</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/turning-off-syntax-highlighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 09:32:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/turning-off-syntax-highlighting/</guid>
      <description>Few weeks back I stumbled on this blog post which stated the obvious benefits of disabling syntax highlighting for your code. I would have been surprised if I hadn&#39;t read this one before. Both the blog posts advocate disabling colors schemes completely or minimally.
At the outset this seems absurd for anyone who has been coding for any length of time and insane for the cool kids who started learning to code in the age of color monitors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Writing on the Internet</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/on-writing-on-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 10:26:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/on-writing-on-internet/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s been a long time since I have written some long form content, and it&#39;s starting to show. The ability to write shows the ability of the mind to sit down and focus. Lately it has been hard to write something down, focus seems to be all over the place. That is hardly surprising given the amount of time I spent on my smartphone.
As important as the writing itself is the Medium(pun intended) and how much control you have over it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>