<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on aswinmohanme</title>
    <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on aswinmohanme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright Aswin Mohan</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aswinmohan.me/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stop Being So Polarized All the Time</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/stop-being-so-polarized-all-the-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/stop-being-so-polarized-all-the-time/</guid>
      <description>Remember when we used to joke around, debate about politics, have a drink afterwards and hug your friend with a different political view. Remember when we would switch on the news and just casually criticize whatever dumb shit both the political parties were doing. Ahh those were the days.
Remember when we used to hug our friends with a slightly different political view than us. Remember when we switch on the news and make fun of whatever dumb shit those politicians were pulling of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Levels of Learning</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/the-levels-of-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 11:08:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/the-levels-of-learning/</guid>
      <description>Everyone loves to learn and with the advent of the Internet and all the good and bad things that came with it, access to a limitless stream of information about any topic under the sun sits on top of the list. I have always tried to learn new things and I love it. I think humans are hardwired to learn about things, their surroundings, friends, the things they could eat, quantum computing, how to lock pick e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MacOS like Fonts on Manjaro/Arch Linux</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/better-fonts-on-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 22:15:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/better-fonts-on-linux/</guid>
      <description>Either you love gorgeous typography or just don&amp;rsquo;t care. If you are the former read ahead on how to make the font rendering on your Linux look just as awesome as that on macOS, else read on to find out what beauty you have been missing.
I switched to a hackintosh for a while and fell in love with how beautiful the typography was. After returning to Linux and some fiddiling around I came across a not so ugly setup that looked close enough to macOS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplicity Matters</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/simplicity-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 09:36:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/simplicity-matters/</guid>
      <description>The world is inherently complex. Countless moving parts interact in exponential ways to create a a beautiful, functional but complex system. Even though the constituent parts of the system are really simple the consequent complex interactions give the system it&amp;rsquo;s unique characteristics. Take the Universe as an example, it&amp;rsquo;s just couple of subatomic particles all interacting within themselves and the ones around them in ways we don&amp;rsquo;t even know exist, which gives the universe it&amp;rsquo;s unique character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compiling OpenSSL 1.0 for Older Package Versions</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/compiling-older-openssl-for-older-packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 21:28:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/compiling-older-openssl-for-older-packages/</guid>
      <description>Running older versions of software is always a pain. There will be missing libraries, compilation errors and what not. These issues can be mitigated little by using a package manager that manages the different versions of the software. But most package managers such as asdf download the source (yea OSS) and compile on your machine.
Most of the tools and libraries work really good, but there is one error that keeps coming again and again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing Autocomplete Select in Rails 6</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/implementing-autocomplete-in-rails-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 13:24:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/implementing-autocomplete-in-rails-6/</guid>
      <description>simple-form makes creating forms that handle associations in rails a breeze. It creates a select dropdown that works really well for use cases where the number of records are few. But once the number of options in the select box gets over a certain number you would be doing your users a favor by implementing it an autocomplete box.
I ran into the same situation. I had a Contact table that has_one: Panchayat relation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Hosted NPM Fonts with Webpack</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/npm-fonts-on-webpack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 12:45:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/npm-fonts-on-webpack/</guid>
      <description>Whenever I wanted new fonts Google Fonts was the defacto place I&amp;rsquo;d go to. It has a ton of great fonts and it&amp;rsquo;s fairly easy to add to your projects. They are also hosted for free by Google which takes some load of your own webserver. I had a personal collection of favorite fonts that I cycle through on new projects.
Everything was going nice when I found out Inter. It was free, looks really crisp and was not available on Google Fonts :(.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Simplest Productivity System is the Best</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/simple-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/simple-productivity/</guid>
      <description>Most of us are productivity gurus on the Internet nowadays. Anyone who works with a computer now has some general ideas of how to achieve productivity and most have those ideas to a fault. There are a million + one articles floating around claiming to have found the secret for eternal productivity. We watch endless motivational videos and informational videos outlining a 99 step process to plan your whole day, another 98 steps to plan your whole week for optimum productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning Off Syntax Highlighting</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/turning-off-syntax-highlighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 09:32:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/turning-off-syntax-highlighting/</guid>
      <description>Few weeks back I stumbled on this blog post which stated the obvious benefits of disabling syntax highlighting for your code. I would have been surprised if I hadn&amp;rsquo;t read this one before. Both the blog posts advocate disabling colors schemes completely or minimally.
At the outset this seems absurd for anyone who has been coding for any length of time and insane for the cool kids who started learning to code in the age of color monitors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Writing on the Internet</title>
      <link>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/on-writing-on-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 10:26:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aswinmohan.me/posts/on-writing-on-internet/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since I have written some long form content, and it&amp;rsquo;s starting to show. The ability to write shows the ability of the mind to sit down and focus. Lately it has been hard to write something down, focus seems to be all over the place. That is hardly surprising given the amount of time I spent on my smartphone.
As important as the writing itself is the Medium(pun intended) and how much control you have over it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
